{
    "id": "104ca6a886e543d4b64309d42b92f798",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is ………………………….. book I have read.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare one person or thing with the whole group to which he/she/it belongs. ",
            "answers": [
                "best",
                "the best",
                "the better"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ………………………….. than anyone I know.",
            "description": "Use the comparative form in expressions with than.",
            "answers": [
                "more generous",
                "most generous",
                "the most generous"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is younger than …………………………..",
            "description": "Object pronouns are considered more appropriate than and as.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ten times …………………………… than I expected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "difficulter",
                "more difficult",
                "most difficult"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ………………………… of all the runners.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fastest",
                "the faster",
                "the fastest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ………………………. than that.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little.",
            "answers": [
                "less expensive",
                "little expensive",
                "lesser expensive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He plays ……………………… than anyone else in the team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "better",
                "more good",
                "the best"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandfather was one of the …………………………….. persons in my neighborhood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the more influential",
                "the most influential",
                "most influential"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have …………………………… interest in economics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "lesser",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………… than stupid.",
            "description": "When we compare two descriptions of the same person, comparatives with more are used.",
            "answers": [
                "more lazy",
                "lazier",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am …………………………….. mother in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "happiest",
                "the happiest",
                "the happier"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ………………………….. of you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the kindest",
                "most kind",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}